{
    "subject": "resource/Lindsay_Pollock",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_art_critics",
    "human_readable": "Lindsay Pollock is a subject of Category:American art critics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9397096037864685,
            "question": "How has Lindsay Pollock influenced the field of American art criticism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8623033761978149,
            "question": "Can you give examples of Lindsay Pollock's work as an art critic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365911245346069,
            "question": "Are there any awards or recognitions associated with Lindsay Pollock's work as an art critic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6883993744850159,
            "question": "What are some key themes or perspectives that Lindsay Pollock often explores in their art critiques?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5915659666061401,
            "question": "What are some notable artists or artworks that Lindsay Pollock has critiqued?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5768826007843018,
            "question": "Is Lindsay Pollock recognized in the art world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5478643774986267,
            "question": "What is Lindsay Pollock known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5203257203102112,
            "question": "Where might you find Lindsay Pollock's writings on art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41932472586631775,
            "question": "What nationality is Lindsay Pollock?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27142369747161865,
            "question": "To which field does Lindsay Pollock belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lindsay Pollock is a subject of Category:American art critics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2023_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Lindsay Pollock?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2023_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find Lindsay Pollock's writings on art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2023_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Lindsay Pollock known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2023_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2023_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided mention Lindsay Pollock as an art reporter and author, editor of Art in America, and writer about the art industry. Additionally, it mentions that she has written for various publications, including ARTnews, Art & Auction, and The Art Newspaper. Furthermore, it highlights her expertise in writing about the art and design world.\n\nCategory:American art critics is a reasonable categorization based on Lindsay Pollock's profession and areas of expertise mentioned in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Lindsay Pollock's career as an art reporter, author, and editor for Art in America. Her work involves writing articles on the art world, which supports her being categorized as an American art critic."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}